It’s him.
Who, Kara?
Who is it?
We need to get Kal.
Now!
Earth's defense’s irreversibly compromised.
Begin the countdown.
Holy…
I am Brainiac
Shattered Alliances Part 5
I seek the one you called Superman.
You have no idea what Brainiac can do.
For years, I believed I have destroyed Krypton.
You're afraid of him.
How do I beat him?
You can't.
Superman’s survival is an oversight I must correct.
I collect worlds,
and then I discard the reminiscence.
NO REMORSE
NO PRISONERS
NO SURVIVORS
I match your strength,
you cannot match my intellect.
Allow me to give you a proper demonstration.
you have a plan?
It's a work in progress.
Earth’s time is up.