Superman’s behind bars.
They couldn't see his good intentions were leading him down a path of tyranny
and evil.
That’s how our greatest hero became our greatest threat.
Shattered Alliances Part 2
Bruce, consider widening your circle of trust.
Nobody wins all by themselves.
Not even you.
We need help, don't we?
Not his.
I’m not that guy anymore.
Look, I get why you don't trust me.
But you should trust the Guardians.
This ring means something.
They put me through hell to get it back.
Don’t worry, Bats.
With this crew on the job, what could go wrong?
What comes next, mere mortals cannot stop.
We both knew it would come to this.
Fate will not spare you.
You wish you had.
LIVE FREE
OR DIE FIGHTING
All day I've been reminded how I feel to be a hero.
How many more innocent people die before you accept that some lives need to be taken?!
The regime is making a comeback.
Not while I'm wearing this ring.
(Wait… so I'm not dreaming?)
This is my fight, Bruce!
You need me!
We both knew it would end this way.